(Leonard:)Okay, let's focus.
(Leonard:)The girls are gone,
we have 48 hours.
(Leonard:)There are no distractions.
Let's change the world.
(Sheldon:)Thinking caps on.
Here we go.
(Raj:)Ooh, this is exciting.
We're innovating.
(Raj:)I feel like
we're in the Facebook movie.
(Howard:)Oh. I never saw that.
Yeah. Really?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Oh.
(Raj:)It's wonderful, and I swear
I'm not saying that
(Raj:)because Justin Timberlake
is in it.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I have it on Blu-ray.
(Sheldon:)We should watch it.
(Raj:)Cool. I'll make the popcorn.
(Leonard:)Guys...
(Leonard:)in 30 seconds, we went from
"Let's change the world"
to "Let's watch TV."
I'm sorry. Is that a "no"?
WOLOWITZ:
Okay. No.
(Howard:)Leonard's right.
We're here to focus.
(Howard:)Didn't we used
to have a list of all our ideas?
I-I think I still have it.
(Sheldon:)I did not get a clear answer.
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna set this down now.
(Leonard:)Ah, here it is.
(laughs)
Whoa.
(Leonard:)I haven't looked
at these in years.
"Robot girlfriend."
(Howard:)Mm, that was mine.
"Robot prostitute."
(Howard:)Also mine.